Clark W. Thompson papers, Inclusive: 1931-1966, undated, Bulk: 1959-1966
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Texas Affairs, 1946-1966, undated; 9
  - Galveston, Galveston, Houston, and Henderson Railway Company Settlement, 1957-1959 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Galveston, Hitchcock Helicopter Base, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Galveston, Honorary Consul of Belgium, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Galveston, "N.S. Savannah" (Nuclear Ship), 1961-1965 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Galveston, Pelican Island, 1965-1966 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Galveston, Purchasing Division of Finance Annual Report, 1964-1965 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Galveston, Seaweed Problem, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Galveston, Saltwater Conversion Plant, 1958-1959 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Galveston, Saltwater Conversion Plant, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Galveston, Saltwater Conversion Plant, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Galveston, Honorary Consul of Peru, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Galveston, Splash Day Celebration, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Galveston, Texas Maritime Academy, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Galveston, Texas Maritime Academy, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Galveston, Texas Maritime Academy, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Galveston, Texas Maritime Academy, 1963-1965 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Galveston, “Use It or Lose It” Investigation, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Galveston, "U.S.S. Galveston" (CLG-3), 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Galveston, University of Texas, Medical Branch, 1959-1962 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Galveston, Weather Bureau, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Galveston, Wharves, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Galveston, Wharves, 1960-1963 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Galveston, Wharves, 1964-1965 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Galveston, Wharves, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Prairie View, Prairie View A&M College, 1953-1962 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Texas City, Seawall and Dike, 1958-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Victoria, General Local Matters, 1961-1962 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Victoria, Around-the-World Trip Promoting the Trail of Six Flags, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Victoria, Devereaux Foundation, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Victoria, Foster Air Force Base, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Victoria, Foster Air Force Base, 1958-1962 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Victoria, Texas National Bank Charter, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Waller, Atomic Research Station, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - West Columbia, West Columbia Bank Charter, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, General, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters, General, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters, General, 1962-1963 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters, General, 1964-1965 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Newsletters, General, 1961 January-March (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Newsletters, General, 1961 April-July (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters, General, 1961 August-December (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, General, 1962 January-March (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, General, 1962 April-July (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, General, 1962 August-December (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, General, 1963 January-March (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, General, 1963 April-July (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, General, 1963 August-December (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, General, 1964 January-July (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, General, 1964 August-September (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, General, 1965 January-April (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, General, 1965 May-July (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters, General, 1965 August-December (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters, General, 1966 January-May (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Hurricane Carla, General (1 of 2), 1961 September (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Hurricane Carla, General (2 of 2), 1961 September-December (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Hurricane Carla, General, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Hurricane Carla, Corps of Engineers After-Action Report, 1962 August (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Hurricane Carla, KGBC Radio Station, undated (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Padre Island, 1960-1962 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Oyster Creek, 1949-1962 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Texas City Disaster, Paper Regarding Legislation, 1952-1953 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Hurricane Carla, Tribute to the News Media, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Brazos River Basin, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Colorado-Lavaca Coastal Basin, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Colorado River Basin, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Cypress Creek Basin, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Guadalupe River Basin, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Lavaca-Guadalupe Coastal Basin, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Lavaca River Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Nueces River Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Nueces-Rio Grande River Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Red River Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Rio Grande Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Sabine River Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, San Antonio-Nueces Costal Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, San Antonio River Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, San Jacinto-Brazos Coastal Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Water Resources Development, Sulphur River Basin, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Rivers and Harbors, General, 1958 January-August (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Rivers and Harbors, General, 1958 September-December (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Rivers and Harbors, General, 1959 January-August (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Rivers and Harbors, General, 1959 September-December (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Rivers and Harbors, General, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Rivers and Harbors, General, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Rivers and Harbors, General, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Bills, S. 3910, 1958 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Bills, H.R. 12955, 1958 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Bills, H.R. 12858, 1958 June (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Bills, H.R. 12858, 1958 July (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Anahuac Channel, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Bauer Dredging Company, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazoria County, Drainage District Number 2 and Velasco-Freeport Levee, 1955-1961 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazoria County, Hurricane and Flood Protection, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Authority, 1954-1955 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Authority, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Authority, 1956 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Authority, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Authority, 1958-1961 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Harbor-Freeport, 1948-1953 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Harbor-Freeport, 1954-1955 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Harbor-Freeport, 1956-1958 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Harbor-Freeport, 1959-1961 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Brazos River Salinity, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Carancahua Bayou, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Clear Creek Lake, 1955-1961 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Clodine Ditch, 1957-1958 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, General, 1948-1954 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, General, 1955-1956 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, General, 1957 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, General, 1958-1959 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, General, 1959-1962 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, H.R. 9859, 1954 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, News Clippings, 1954-1960 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, Public Hearing, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, Review of Report, 1956 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Colorado River Navigation, Review of Report, undated (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Columbus Bend Dam (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Columbus Bend Dam (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Columbus Bend Dam (1 of 3), 1961 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Columbus Bend Dam (2 of 3), 1961 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Columbus Bend Dam (3 of 3), 1961 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Columbus Bend Dam, 1962 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Corps of Engineers, 1955-1962 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Cummins Creek, 1956-1958 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Dickinson Bayou, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Double Bayou, 1959-1960 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Rivers and Harbors, East Bay Bayou Watershed, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Ferguson Reservoir, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Flores Bayou, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Fort Bend County Drainage District, 1953-1956 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Freeport Harbor, 1959-1962 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Galveston, East End Flats, 1962 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Galveston Harbor and Houston Ship Channel, 1957-1960 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Galveston Seawall, General, 1948-1949 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Galveston Seawall, General, 1950-1953 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Galveston Seawall, General, 1954-1957 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Galveston Seawall, General, 1958-1961 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Galveston Seawall, Maps, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Galveston Seawall, News Clippings, 1948-1954 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe-Blanco River Authority, 1950-1954 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe-Blanco River Authority, 1955 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe-Blanco River Authority, 1956-1957 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe-Blanco River Authority, 1958-1962 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe-Blanco River Authority, Audit Report, 1949 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe-Blanco River Authority, Audit Report, 1956 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe-Blanco River Authority, Audit Report, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe River Channel, Seadrift to Victoria, 1950-1958 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe River Channel, Seadrift to Victoria, 1958-1962 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Guadalupe River Channel, Seadrift to Victoria, H.R. 6812, 1952 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Hearings, 1959 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Hurricane Study Program for Texas Coast, 1961-1962 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lavaca and Navidad, Request by Clark Thompson to Review Reports, 1951 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lavaca and Navidad, River Flood Control Project, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lavaca and Navidad, River Flood Control Project, 1952-1953 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lavaca and Navidad, River Flood Control Project, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lavaca and Navidad, River Flood Control Project, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lavaca and Navidad, River Flood Control Project, General, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lavaca and Navidad, River Flood Control Project, Photos, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lavaca and Navidad, River Flood Control Project, 1958 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lavaca and Navidad, River Flood Control Project, 1959-1962 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Lower Colorado River Authority and Flood Control, 1947-1962 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Matagorda River, 1960-1961 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Matagorda Shipping Channel, General, 1954-1955 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Matagorda Shipping Channel, General, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Matagorda Shipping Channel, General, 1957-1958 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Matagorda Shipping Channel, General, 1959 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Matagorda Shipping Channel, General, 1960-1962 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Matagorda Shipping Channel, News Clippings, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Mill Creek, 1946 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Mill Creek, 1948 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Mill Creek, 1949-1950 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Mill Creek, 1951-1961 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Missouri-Pacific Bridge, 1958-1962 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Moses Lake Harbor of Refuge, 1960-1962 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Navasota River-Millican Dam, 1960-1962 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Pass Cavallo, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Pass Cavallo, 1951-1953 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Pass Cavallo, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Pass Cavallo, 1949-1955 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Pass Cavallo, 1955-1956 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Pass Cavallo, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Plum Creek, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Port Lavaca, 1960-1961 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Rivers and Harbors and Beach Erosion Omnibus Bill, H.R. 12080, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Sam Rayburn Reservoir, McGee Bend Dam, 1958-1962 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Rivers and Harbors, San Antonio Bay, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Rivers and Harbors, San Leon Channel, 1957-1961 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Surfside Bridge Spoil Easement, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Trinity River, 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Turkey Creek, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Rives and Harbors, Texas City Channel, General, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Rives and Harbors, Texas City Channel, General, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Rives and Harbors, Texas City Channel, General, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Rives and Harbors, Texas City Channel, General, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Rives and Harbors, Texas City Channel, General, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Rives and Harbors, Texas City Channel, General, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Texas City Channel, Letters from Secretary of the Army, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Wallisville Dam, Correspondence (1 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Wallisville Dam, Correspondence (2 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Wallisville Dam, Correspondence (3 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Wallisville Dam, Legislation and Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Rivers and Harbors, Wallisville Dam, Questions and Answers, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Texas City Disaster, Awards for Deaths, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Texas City Disaster, Blank Claims Statement, undated (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Texas City Disaster, Claims, 1953-1955 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Texas City Disaster, Claims, 1957-1958 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Texas City Disaster, Claims, 1959-1962 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Texas City Disaster, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Texas City Disaster, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1954 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Texas City Disaster, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1954 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Texas City Disaster, Correspondence (1 of 3), 1955 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Texas City Disaster, Correspondence (2 of 3), 1955 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Texas City Disaster, Correspondence (3 of 3), 1955 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Texas City Disaster, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Texas City Disaster, Correspondence, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Texas City Disaster, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Texas City Disaster, “Death on the Waterfront” by Milton Mackaye, undated (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Texas City Disaster, Facts and Figures, 1948 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.J.R. 172, 80th Congress, 1947 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 669, 80th Congress, 1948 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 296, 83rd Congress, 1953 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 8528, 83rd Congress, 1954 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 8572, 83rd Congress, 1954 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 7258, 83rd Congress, 1954 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 9785, 83rd Congress, 1954 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Texas City Disaster, S. 1077, 84th Congress, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 4045, 84th Congress, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Texas City Disaster, S. 1077 and H.R. 4045, 84th Congress, Hearings, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 9138, 84th Congress, 1956 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 9290, 84th Congress, 1956 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 11499, 84th Congress, 1956 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 12230, 85th Congress, 1958 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 12378, 85th Congress, 1958 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 1973, 86th Congress, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Texas City Disaster, H.R. 4821, 86th Congress, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Texas City Disaster, Information Requests, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Texas City Disaster, Litigation with France (1 of 4), 1948 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Texas City Disaster, Litigation with France (2 of 4), 1948 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Texas City Disaster, Litigation with France (3 of 4), 1948 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Texas City Disaster, Litigation with France (4 of 4), 1948 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Texas City Disaster, News Clippings, 1954-1958 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation, 1952-1953 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation, 1955 January-July (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation, 1955 August-December (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation, 1956 May-December (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation (1 of 2), 1958 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation (2 of 2), 1958 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation, 1959 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Texas City Disaster, Papers Regarding Legislation, 1960-1966 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Texas City Disaster, Photographs, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Texas City Disaster, Relief Program (1 of 3), undated (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Texas City Disaster, Relief Program (2 of 3), undated (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Texas City Disaster, Relief Program (3 of 3), undated (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Texas City Disaster, Report on an Investigation of Ammonium Nitrate, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Supreme Court, "Dalenite v. United States", 1952 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Texas City School District Claim, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Correspondence, Information Requests, "Congressional Record", 1963-1966 (Box 96, Folder 4)